advertisingweek.eu 2013-12-27

# Advertising Week Europe 2014 – London [ March 31 - 4 April ] / Privacy Policy

Welcome to www.advertisingweek.eu (the “Website”) operated by Advertising Week, Inc., located at 131 West 33rd Street, Suite 800, New York, NY 10001 (“AW”, “we”, “our”, or “us”). This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you about how your personally identifiable information (“PII”) and other information is collected by us in operating the Website.

To assist you in reading our Privacy Policy, we have provided answers to the following frequently asked questions:

  * How does the Website work?

  * What type of PII does AW collect from you and how do we use it?

  * What other information does AW collect?

  * How do we store information?

  * Does AW provide links to other websites?

  * What are our policies regarding children?

  * Do we have a mechanism to address complaints about the handling of information that we collect?

  How does the Website work?  
The Website offers visitors to the Website (“you” or “your”) the opportunity to browse the Website and use certain features on the Website. By using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of your information by AW as described herein. AW reserves the right to change how we handle the information we collect through the Website at any time. We will update this Privacy Policy to reflect any changes in our privacy collection and handling practices, and will indicate that changes to this Privacy Policy have been made by listing a new date under “Last Modified” at the end of this Agreement. Such changes will take effect immediately once posted to the Website.

  What type of PII does AW collect from you and how do we use it?  
AW does not require you to provide us with any PII. Unless you provide your PII to AW through the Website, we will not collect any PII from you. However, in order to  
use certain functionality (including, for example, to subscribe to our newsletters) on the Website, to participate in promotions offered from time to time or to purchase  
products through the Website, you will need to provide certain PII to us.

  Under what circumstances may we share your PII?  
AW will share your PII with other entities who work on our behalf or with us. These entities may use your PII to help fulfill your requests in connection with the  
Website and to help us communicate with you about different resources offered as part of the Website. Also, our parent, subsidiary and affiliate companies, or  
entities to which any of our assets, products, sites or operations may be transferred, will be able to use your PII.

  On occasion, AW may share your PII with third parties for marketing purposes. If you would rather us not share your PII with any third party for direct marketing  
purposes, please either (1) do not submit PII to AW through the Website or (2) indicate your desire for us not to share your PII with third parties for direct  
marketing purposes by submitting such a request in writing (an “Opt-Out Request”) to us at: Advertising Week Europe, 131 West 33rd Street, New York, NY 10001,  
Attn: Legal or by using the following link at optout@advertisingweek.eu.

  Please note that it may take time for us to comply with your Opt-Out Request and, in the interim, we may continue to use your PII as described in this Privacy  
Policy. In addition, please note that after receiving your Opt-Out Request, we may continue to maintain your name and other PII to help us ensure we can honor  
such request, to communicate to you about your account, and for other purposes not related to direct marketing.

  If we receive your Opt-Out Request after having shared your PII with a third party, AW may not be able to control use of such PII by such third party (or any  
other party to whom such third party may have transferred your PII). In such an event you agree that AW shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for damages or loss caused or alleged to be caused in connection with the use of such PII by any such third party or resulting from any such transfer or disposition. If you are concerned about AW sharing your PII with third parties or otherwise transferring or disposing your PII, you should not provide your PII to AW.

  We may also release your PII to third parties if we believe such release is necessary (i) to comply with the law (e.g., a legal process or a statutory  
authorization), (ii) to apply or enforce our user agreements, (iii) to protect our rights or property, (iv) as part of a corporate reorganization,  
consolidation, merger, or sale of substantially all of the assets of AW, or (v) if we reasonably believe that a danger to any person requires disclosure of such PII.

  What other information does AW collect?  
We also may collect anonymous and aggregate information from you about your preferences in navigating the Website by using cookies, action tags and other  
methods. Cookies are small text files that identify your computer. We may use cookies to, among other things, monitor Website usage, customize Website  
features, identify your computer’s operating system and browser, and complete transactions. An action tag is a small, graphic image on a webpage that is designed to allow the website owner or a third party to monitor who is visiting a website by collecting the IP address of the computer to which the tag is  
sent, the URL of the webpage that the tag comes from and the time that such webpage was viewed. Tags may be associated with cookie information. We may  
also use such non-PII for promotional purposes.

  If you do not want us to track such information about you, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse cookies when your  
browser alerts you to their presence. You can also adjust the settings in your browser to refuse all cookies.

  How do we store information?  
While we take reasonable efforts to protect PII provided to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be lost, disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others.

  Does AW provide links to other websites?  
AW may provide links to other websites or resources of possible interest to you. Because we have no control over unaffiliated websites to which we provide links, the collection and use of your PII and other information by such websites shall be subject to the policies and procedures of such websites and not this Privacy Policy.

  What are our policies regarding children?  
You must be eighteen (18) years of age or older in order to use the Website. AW does not knowingly collect PII from anyone under thirteen (13) years of age.

  Do we have a mechanism to address complaints about the handling of information that we collect?  
If you have questions or concerns about any of our information collection or handling practices, please contact us by e-mail at info@advertisingweek.eu or  
write to us at Advertising Week Europe, 131 West 33rd Street, Suite 800, New York, NY 10001, Attention: Privacy Policy.

Last Update: December, 2012
